Sir, please take a seat over here.
Okay.
How are things between you two right now?
That's not the point.
I'm sorry.
This part is very important.
So your feelings for your wife...
haven't changed at all?
No.
How long has it been since you were intimate?
That... That's not the point.
This is very important.
We agreed
to be honest with each other.
Not since then.
Why is that?
It's just...
It's because...
I get scared.
Scared of losing again.
Have you considered having another child?
Yes, yes.
What made you consider
having another one?
With this whole thing...
maybe we could... could move past it.
Because...
that's exactly where the root problem lies.
Can I speak to you in private?
Is that okay?
Sorry, um...
could you step out for a moment?
I'm sorry.
Aren't you going to hit me?
Why would I hit you
to punish you?
Go ahead.
Hit me wherever you want.
How did we
end up like this?
Have you been waiting long?
I just met with a client.
Okay, let's order... order something.
No, it's fine. No need.
How long have you been back?
A couple of days.
How's Mom?
She's fine. Everything's good.
Didn't you say you had something urgent?
What is it?
I was thinking...
let's get a divorce if there's really no other way.
"Really no other way"...
Why phrase it like that?
I... I don't want this either.
But...
we just can't solve this problem right now.
You... you keep saying it yourself.
You always think of him.
Don't you?
I do.
That's why I said we can't solve this.
This is the only option we have left.
On my end,
I've... I've tried everything I could.
Tried
to do what?
I...
I've been explaining it to you.
I've been trying to lay out
the whole story clearly for you.
I've been analyzing it for you.
Yeah, you explained it very clearly.
And analyzed it very thoroughly.
Okay, I agree.
You... you agree to...
I agree to the divorce.
So you...
think that I did something wrong?
No.
You were perfect.
What's wrong with your voice?
My voice?
It's hoarse.
You sound like Donald Duck.
Dr. Li.
We asked you here today
mainly to ask you a few things.
When Xie Xin and his wife were in your office,
what did you talk about?
What happened?
They came for relationship counseling.
Let me explain.
We did run into a few minor issues back then
in our marriage.
It's normal for couples to have issues.
Xie Xin was busy.
We did communicate less.
So we went to see Dr. Li
for some relationship counseling.
It's true. We hadn't for a long time...
We hadn't sat down for a proper talk, right?
Right, right.
And what was this minor issue?
They had a child before.
A child?
Yes, yes.
We did have a child.
We did.
Since it was my first pregnancy,
I wasn't very careful.
I ate lots of raw and cold food, and...
sadly, I ended up in the hospital.
How did you get there?
We took a car.
We drove.
Who drove the car?
I did... No.
I drove.
No, Xie Xin.
I had a bit to drink.
You're remembering it wrong.
That day was...
our wedding anniversary.
And we were having such a wonderful time
at a really beautiful restaurant, right?
You even ordered a steak for me,
and some cake.
And we were so, so happy that day.
And then...
my... my stomach started hurting.
And I had a little to drink.
No, no.
Xie Xin, you're really remembering it wrong.
It was... it was that delivery rider.
That delivery rider ran a red light.
That's why we...
But if I hadn't been drinking,
I could have reacted in time. No.
It had nothing to do with that!
Xie Xin. Xie Xin!
Listen to me.
It wasn't like that.
He clearly ran the red light!
Okay, okay, okay.
Xie Xin.
Let me explain, okay?
Come, come, come here. Come.
Let me explain.
The wedding anniversary was...
It really was our anniversary. We also had...
a delicious steak.
Just like my Honey said.
And I did have some to drink.
But because my Honey was
having such bad stomach pains,
I didn't call a sober driver service.
I insisted on driving her to the hospital myself.
We hit the delivery rider.
I slammed on the brakes.
When I looked at her again,
her...
her dress was already covered in red.
When we got to the hospital...
Yeah, right.
Then what is the real reason for the divorce?
Why divorce? Why get a divorce?
You're being a bit too good to me.
Let me just say this.
You have no idea how the people before chewed me out.
Still saving face for me, really.
You really do know me.
The thing is... I
am someone who easily
runs away or, let's say,
avoids problems.
Throughout my life, it's always been
my Honey who tolerates and guides me.
She treats me really well.
About this divorce thing,
I actually said it was about the child then.
But...
Are you afraid someone can't hear or what?
Turn this up for me.
About the divorce,
I... I lied to you.
What I said back then was
I couldn't... I... I couldn't face the child.
But actually, it's because I couldn't face
the fact that it seemed I caused
this outcome.
So I... I owe you an apology.
I'm sorry, Honey.
Are you going to hit me or what?
Are you going to...
Having fun?
I am.
What's the score?
Ten to twelve.
Okay.
Come on, Honey.
Do you want to get shocked?
Not really, actually.
I'm a bit tired.
But I don't want you getting shocked either.
Alright.
Come on.
I forfeit.
Zhang Ya chose to forfeit.
There are no losers in this round.
And no one will be punished.
No, you are.
You're not just a Psycho,
you're also a liar.
Why didn't you tell me this rule earlier?
I got beaten up like this,
and shocked so many times.
If I knew, I could've just done that.
Whatever, forget it.
Didn't you have five people?
Hurry up, bring the other two up.
So far, Old Lin, my bro, my Honey.
Who else?
Could it be my parents?
You even ordered takeout?
You won't have time to eat it.
I'm wrapping this up quickly.
Bro, you...
No, don't come up here.
Leave it at the door.
Leave it at the door. It's dangerous here.
It's all electrified.
You... hurry up and get down.
Next person. Name.
Wang Ke.
Okay, Wang Ke. Never heard of him.
I am Wang Ke.
Do we know each other?